{
  "type": "rome2hira",
  "level": "YOUON",
  "questions": [
    { "prompt": "kya", "answer": "きゃ" },
    { "prompt": "kyu", "answer": "きゅ" },
    { "prompt": "kyo", "answer": "きょ" },
    { "prompt": "sha", "answer": "しゃ" },
    { "prompt": "shu", "answer": "しゅ" },
    { "prompt": "sho", "answer": "しょ" },
    { "prompt": "cha", "answer": "ちゃ" },
    { "prompt": "chu", "answer": "ちゅ" },
    { "prompt": "cho", "answer": "ちょ" },
    { "prompt": "nya", "answer": "にゃ" },
    { "prompt": "nyu", "answer": "にゅ" },
    { "prompt": "nyo", "answer": "にょ" },
    { "prompt": "hya", "answer": "ひゃ" },
    { "prompt": "hyu", "answer": "ひゅ" },
    { "prompt": "hyo", "answer": "ひょ" },
    { "prompt": "mya", "answer": "みゃ" },
    { "prompt": "myu", "answer": "みゅ" },
    { "prompt": "myo", "answer": "みょ" },
    { "prompt": "rya", "answer": "りゃ" },
    { "prompt": "ryu", "answer": "りゅ" },
    { "prompt": "ryo", "answer": "りょ" },
    { "prompt": "gya", "answer": "ぎゃ" },
    { "prompt": "gyu", "answer": "ぎゅ" },
    { "prompt": "gyo", "answer": "ぎょ" },
    { "prompt": "ja", "answer": "じゃ" },
    { "prompt": "ju", "answer": "じゅ" },
    { "prompt": "jo", "answer": "じょ" },
    { "prompt": "bya", "answer": "びゃ" },
    { "prompt": "byu", "answer": "びゅ" },
    { "prompt": "byo", "answer": "びょ" },
    { "prompt": "pya", "answer": "ぴゃ" },
    { "prompt": "pyu", "answer": "ぴゅ" },
    { "prompt": "pyo", "answer": "ぴょ" }
  ]
}
